{
    "subject": "resource/Nathan_Phelps",
    "predicate": "property/residence",
    "object": "resource/Calgary",
    "human_readable": "Nathan Phelps resided in Calgary.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869090914726257,
            "question": "Is Calgary the location where Nathan Phelps resided?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848464488983154,
            "question": "Is Calgary known as the home of Nathan Phelps?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678275465965271,
            "question": "What city was Nathan Phelps associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6377239227294922,
            "question": "Where is Nathan Phelps currently located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6349000334739685,
            "question": "What city would you find Nathan Phelps in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6127112507820129,
            "question": "Nathan Phelps lived in which Canadian city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5732253789901733,
            "question": "Where did Nathan Phelps live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5104725360870361,
            "question": "In which city did Nathan Phelps make his home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48106735944747925,
            "question": "What is the location of Nathan Phelps' residence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4186807870864868,
            "question": "Can you tell me a fact about Nathan Phelps' residence?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathan Phelps resided in Calgary.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5525_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the location of Nathan Phelps' residence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5525_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city did Nathan Phelps make his home?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5525_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Nathan Phelps live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5525_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5525_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Nate Phelps currently resides in Calgary, Alberta. The relevant text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5525/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt states:\n\n\"Phelps later moved to rural British Columbia, Canada, and currently lives in Calgary, Alberta.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Nathan Phelps \"currently lives in Calgary, Alberta,\" which supports the statement that Nathan Phelps resided in Calgary."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}